1728.com 2019-08-01

# Privacy Policy Statement

This policy was last updated on May 5, 2009.

Privacy Policy for www.1728.com

At www.1728.com, we recognize that privacy of personal information is important.  
We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Listed below are the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit www.1728.com, and how we safeguard your information.

**Log Files**  
_As with most other websites_ , we collect and use the data contained in log files.  
The information in the log files include:  
• your IP (internet protocol) address  
• your Internet Service Provider  
• the browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Google Chrome) that you used when you visited our site   
• the time you visited our site  
• which pages you visited throughout our site

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We also use third party advertisements on www.1728.com to support our site.  
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Return To Home Page
